{
    "subject": "resource/Claudia_Jordan",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Providence,_Rhode_Island",
    "human_readable": "Claudia Jordan was born in Providence, Rhode Island.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8961352109909058,
            "question": "Where was Claudia Jordan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7941080331802368,
            "question": "When was Claudia Jordan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5993353724479675,
            "question": "What is Claudia Jordan's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5185791850090027,
            "question": "What state is Providence, Rhode Island in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4281671643257141,
            "question": "Is Claudia Jordan known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.409035325050354,
            "question": "What is Claudia Jordan's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34466448426246643,
            "question": "Where did Claudia Jordan go to school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33161064982414246,
            "question": "Does Claudia Jordan have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32597288489341736,
            "question": "What are some of Claudia Jordan's notable roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17318293452262878,
            "question": "Has Claudia Jordan appeared on any reality television shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claudia Jordan was born in Providence, Rhode Island.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8169_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Claudia Jordan's notable roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8169_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Claudia Jordan have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8169_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Claudia Jordan go to school?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8169_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8169_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents support this triple as it is mentioned in multiple files (e.g. file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8169/re-ranker-msmarco/53.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8169/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt, etc.) that Claudia Jordan was born in Providence, Rhode Island."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Claudia Jordan was born on April 12, 1973, in Providence, Rhode Island. Therefore, the statement \"Claudia Jordan was born in Providence, Rhode Island\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}